{
    "id": "f4657c27597c44afa2ed59eca847e20c",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………. my sons can drive.",
            "description": "We use neither of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "918c6f762d654d40a96b89df2f9fc14a"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. them was there.",
            "description": "We use neither of before a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "118c18cc623744b99f5666e931b4c6c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… answer is correct.",
            "description": "Neither is used without of before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3338d6ebd8e348da8be7622f5b79c29f"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I can’t dance.’ ‘………………………. can I.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3bc41b7d8c3042ba8f69588c73595cdd"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘She can’t swim.’ ‘I can’t ………………………’",
            "description": "Can’t either means the same as neither can.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6afe2260ae9849868cba9a7da7cff967"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t travel ………………………… these days.",
            "description": "Much can be used as an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "a lot",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a4293a063676424d8b07840c8157a388"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got ……………………….. time.",
            "description": "Plenty of is mainly used in affirmative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "plenty of",
                "much",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7153f4edb334357ae09c425e80267a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got ……………………………. women friends but she doesn’t know …………………..  men.",
            "description": "Many is mainly used in negative and interrogative sentences. In affirmative clauses we prefer plenty of or a lot of.",
            "answers": [
                "many, a lot of",
                "many, many",
                "a lot of, many"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d1859045dcb348578fc3cf7dd7f720cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "You haven’t eaten ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "a lot",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ff5a729f6709454091b9c9a33b31b065"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. cheese is made from cow milk.",
            "description": "We use most before a noun without a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Much",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac1af991c8744433b54141f10b666674"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… my friends are non-smokers.",
            "description": "We use most of before a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "762512a28b624e7fb7f0f9995a98461b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t pass the exam. I could not answer ………………………….. the questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2437ad5f2ac042c7a6e606690e625084"
        }
    ]
}